Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Field Recordings AIA.031.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Public Performances, 1965-1997, Jun 25, 1965-Feb 22, 1997
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival, Philadelphia, PA. (Folder two) Fiddle workshop with Tony Demarco, Eugene O'Donnell, James Kelly, Ed Reavy (fiddles). Song and ballad workshop with Fr. Charlie Coen, Richard Hughes, Brian Brooks, Daithi Sproule, Mick Moloney, Tim Lyons and Mike Flynn (vocals). Traditional music played for a ceili by Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) and Mick Moloney (banjo), Unidentified (whistle). Step dance workshop with music by Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Mick Moloney (guitar). Concert performances by Celtic Thunder and DeDanann. (Four CDs – Total length: 03:04:47) aiamm224C, 225C, 226C, Sep 17, 1978; aiamm224C, aiamm225C, aiamm226C (Box 11, Box 34, Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival, Philadelphia, PA. (Folder three) Daytime and evening concert performances by DeDanann: Frankie Gavin (fiddle), Alec Finn (bouzouki), Jackie Daly (accordion), Johnny "Ringo" McDonagh (bodhran, bones), Tim Lyons (vocals), Charlie Piggott (banjo) (Two CDs – Total length: 00:56:28) aiamm 224C, 225C, Sep 17, 1978; 224C, aiamm225C (Box 34, Box 5, Folder 38, Box 11)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. "Tape 5 - Evening Concert - Tape 2." Musicians include: Mick Moloney, Eugene O'Donnell, Larry McCullough and Devlish Mary, Richard Hughes, Flying Cloud, Bill Ochs, James Kelly, Daithi Sproule. aiamm517R, Sep 16, 1978; aiamm517R (Box 58, Box 19)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. "Tape 6: James Kelly, Paddy O'Brien, Daithi Sproule, DeDanaan." aiamm516R, Sep 16, 1978; aiamm516R (Box 19, Box 58)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. "4th Annual." Wind instrument workshop MCed by L E McCullough with Bill Ochs and Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Richard Hughes, Jack Coen and Linda Hickman (flutes), Peter Healon and concert performances by Flying Cloud, Sean McGlynn (accordion), Jack Coen (flute) and Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo). (Total length: 01:30:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center. aiamm904C, Sep 17, 1978; aiamm904C (Box 25, Box 52)
  - "Session at Kelly's, Boston, MA." aiamm905C, Nov 1, 1978; aiamm905C (Box 27, Box 52)
  - Concert at the Cherry Tree: Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo, mandolin and vocals) Concert performance at the Cherry Tree Folk Co-op, Philadelphia, PA. (Two CDs – Total length 01:11:54) aiamm126R, 314C, Nov, 1978; aiamm126R, aiamm314C (Box 5, Folder 39, Box 31, Box 11, Box 12, Box 34)
  - McComiskey, Billy; Moloney, Mick in Bethlehem, PA. aiamm1320C, Nov 1978; aiamm1320C (Box 74, Box 44)
  - Irish Festival in Landsdale, PA. aiamm617R, 1978; aiamm617R (Box 76)
  - Irish Festival 9/78, Lansdale, PA. [SUPER 8 FILM]. aiamm521R, Sep, 1978; aiamm521R (Box 19)
  - "Session in Wilkes Barre, PA." Musicians include Sean McGlynn (accordion), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Mick Moloney (banjo). (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm508R, Jan 29, 1978; aiamm508R (Box 39, Box 16)
  - Moloney, Mick (mandolin, guitar, vocals), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle) Concert performance in Philadelphia. (One CD – Length: 00:34:45) aiamm126R, 326R, March 1979; aiamm126R, aiamm326R (Box 31, Box 9, Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Session at Moloney's. House session with Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Micheal O'Suilleabhan, Noirin Ni Rian, Mike Flynn (vocals), Jane Meehan in Philadelphia, PA. (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm906C, Apr 3, 1979; aiamm906C (Box 39, Box 25)
  - "Hopkinson - Evening Concert." Irish segment of a concert MCed by Moloney. Musicians include: Jimmy Devine (fiddle), Timmy Britton (uilleann pipes), Tom Harrigan (Flute), Andy O'Brien (vocals, guitar), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Brendan and Martin Mulvihill (fiddles), L.E. McCullogh (whistle), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Mike Flynn (vocals), Gail Mulvihill (banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Mick Moloney (banjo), Barbara Golden and Steve Gallagher (dancers). (Length: 00:30:00). aiamm524R, Apr 29, 1979; aiamm524R (Box 39, Box 16)
  - "Evening Concert - Hopkinson - Tape 1." aiamm525R, Apr 29, 1979; aiamm525R (Box 19)
    This reel is blank.
  - Touring Group Session in Puerto, Rico (Possibly Green Fields of America). aiamm1271C, May 1, 1979; aiamm1271C (Box 44, Box 68)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Jack Coen (flute, whistle), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina, vocals, whistle), Liz Carroll (fiddle, piano, whistle), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) and Bill Ochs (uilleann pipes, whistle). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:01:21) aiamm304R, 305R, May 5, 1979; aiamm304R, aiamm305R (Box 33, Box 12, Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Washington, D.C. Musicians: Jack Coen (flute, whistle), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina, vocals, whistle), Liz Carroll (fiddle, piano, whistle), Bill Ochs (uilleann pipes, whistle), Donny Golden (dancer), Michael Flatley (dancer, flute). (One CD – Length: 00:32:41) aiamm306R, May 6, 1979; aiamm306R (Box 6, Folder 3, Box 33, Box 12)
  - Session at Frank Claudy's, Washington, D.C. Musicians include: Frank Claudy (flute), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Sean McGlynn (accordion). (One CD – Length: 00:27:55) aiamm261, May 6, 1979-May 7, 1979; aiamm261 (Box 6, Folder 4, Box 12)
  - Green Fields of America (group) End of a concert in Youngstown, Ohio. Musicians include Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo), Fr. Charlie Coen (melodeon). (Length: 00:15:00). aiamm526R, May 17, 1979; aiamm526R (Box 39, Box 16)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Omaha, NE. (Tape indicates last track recorded in Youngstown, OH) Musicians: Jack Coen (flute, whistle), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina, vocals, whistle), Liz Carroll (fiddle, piano, whistle), Bill Ochs (uilleann pipes, whistle), Donny Golden (dancer), Michael Flatley (dancer, flute). (One CD – Length: 00:29:11) aiamm222C, May 1979; aiamm222C (Box 34, Box 11, Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Session at Moloney's. Musicians: Paddy O'Brien (accordion, b. 1945, Daingean, Co. Offaly), Mike Flynn (vocals, b. Co. Clare), Mick Moloney (banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle). Traditional music and conversation recorded in Philadelphia, PA. (Four CDs – Total length: 02:39:42) aiamm183C, 272C, Jun 13, 1979; aiamm183C, aiamm272C (Box 34, Box 12, Box 6, Folder 6)
  - "Martin O'Connor: New Canaan and Philadelphia." aiamm908C, Jul 22, 1979 and Jul 30, 1979; aiamm908C (Box 52, Box 27)
  - Celtic Thunder (group) Concert performance in Bluemont, VA. labeled " for Mick Moloney only." (Length: 00:30:00) aiamm907C, Jun 30, 1979; aiamm907C (Box 25, Box 52)
  - Session in Woodford, Co. Galway. Musicians include Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina) and Moloney (banjo). (Length: 00:50:00) aiamm909C, Aug 1, 1979; aiamm909C (Box 25, Box 52)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. Concert performances in Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Jack Coen (flute), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mick Moloney (guitar) (20 minutes); Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) (30 minutes); Celtic Thunder (25 minutes); Sean McGlynn (accordion), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina) (20 minutes); Timmy Britton (uilleann pipes) (10 minutes) (Total length: 01:30:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center. aiamm910C, Sep 17, 1979; aiamm910C (Box 25, Box 39)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. Evening concert performance in Philadelphia, PA. Musicians include: Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Unidentified (dancers), Larry (L.E.) McCullough (whistle, flute) and Devlish Mary, Richard Hughes (flute), The Flying Cloud: Tony DeMarco (fiddle), Brian Brooks (vocals, mandolin), Caesar Pacifici (guitar). (Four CDs – Total length: 01:35:39) aiamm333C, Sep 17, 1979; aiamm333C (Box 34, Box 13, Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Moloney, Mick (educator) Lecture entitled "Improvisation in Irish Music," with examples of sean nos singing and instrumental music from Martin O'Connor (accordion) as part of Making Music Together lecture series for the Folklife Center at International House, Philadelphia, PA. (Length: 02:00:00). aiamm527R, Oct 11, 1979; aiamm527R (Box 16, Box 39)
  - "Reel 2 of 2 - Side 2 - Music Blank Music." aiamm528R, Oct 11, 1979; aiamm528R (Box 58, Box 19)
  - Clannad. Concert performance at the International House, Philadelphia, PA. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:29:04) aiamm179C, Nov 4, 1979; aiamm179C (Box 34, Box 10, Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Heaney, Joe (sean nos singer). Concert performance at the Denver Folklore Center Concert Hall for the Swallow Hill Music Association, recorded by [?]. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:35:10) aiamm345C, Nov 4, 1979; aiamm345C (Box 13, Box 6, Folder 9, Box 34)
  - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Seattle, WA. Musicians: Al Purcell (uilleann pipes, whistle), Mike Rafferty (flute), Mick Moloney (banjo, mandolin), Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Andy O'Brien (guitar, vocals), Michael Flatley, Donny Golden (dancing). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:35:36) aiamm165C, Nov 11, 1979; aiamm165C (Box 34, Box 6, Folder 10, Box 10)
  - Green Fields of America; Springfield, Missouri (Side 3 of 3). aiamm1250C, Nov 16, 1979; aiamm1250C (Box 44, Box 68)
  - Session in Weston, CT. Musicians include: Billy McComiskey, Sean McGlynn (accordions), Mick Moloney (banjo), Andy O'Brien (guitar). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:33:07) aiamm156C, Dec 15, 1979; aiamm156C (Box 6, Folder 11, Box 10, Box 34)
  - "Best of Irish Music and Dance in America – Lowell – 1." aiamm523R, 1979; aiamm523R (Box 58, Box 24)
  - "Best of Irish etc.- Lowell - 3." aiamm522R, 1979; aiamm522R (Box 58, Box 24)
  - New England Celebration. aiamm1362C, 1979; aiamm1362C (Box 44, Box 70)
  - "ISSTC Session." Side A: Large session at Irish Arts Center with Bill Ochs (uilleann pipes), Margaret Barry (vocals) unidentified fiddles, drum kit, bodhran, whistle, guitar, poetry reading, songs and enthusiastic crowd (60 minutes); Side B: Large session continued including songs performed by Margaret Barry (vocals, banjo). (60 minutes) (Total length: 02:00:00) aiamm529R, 1970s; aiamm529R (Box 57, Box 23)
  - "Lisdoonvarna Session." Small session in Co. Clare with Moloney (banjo), and unidentified fiddle, whistle, bodhran, songs and stories.(Length: 01:00:00) aiamm915C, 1970s; aiamm915C (Box 25, Box 52)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. Concert performances by Clannad and DeDanaan. (Total length: 01:30:00) aiamm914C, 1970s; aiamm914C (Box 25, Box 55)
  - "Sessions in Lisdoonvarna and Drogheda." Session with stories and songs in Lisdoonvarna, Co. Clare; smaller session in Drogheda, Co. Louth with Moloney (mandolin, vocals) and unidentified whistle and guitar. (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm911C, early 1970s; aiamm911C (Box 25, Box 52)
  - "Best of Folklife Center of International House." Concert performances by various ethnic ensembles (Cambodian, Balkan...) in Philadelphia, PA. hosted by Moloney. (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm913C, late 1970s; aiamm913C (Box 25, Box 39)
  - Long Note. Irish radio program profiling Moloney. (Length: 00:45:00). aiamm912C, late 1970s; aiamm912C (Box 25, Box 39)
  - Long Note. Irish radio program. aiamm1354C, late 1970s; aiamm1354C (Box 44, Box 72)
  - Slattery's Session. aiamm1381C, late 1970s; aiamm1381C (Box 71, Box 44)
  - "Mahon, McComiskey, Considine" aiamm1203C, 1970s; aiamm1203C (Box 64, Box 27)
  - Session in San Francisco, CA. Musicians: Denis Brooks (uilleann pipes), Richard Twomey (fiddle), Peter Weelan (bouzouki, vocals), Mike Deely (bodhran, bones). (One CD – Length: 00:13:44) aiamm40R, 1970s; aiamm40R (Box 6, Folder 12, Box 28, Box 8)
  - Session in Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Sean McGlynn (accordion), Jack Coen (flute), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (guitar). (One CD – Length: 00:45:15) aiamm18R, Mar 16,1980; aiamm18R (Box 6, Folder 13, Box 8, Box 28)
  - "St. Pat's at Cherry Tree - Reel 5 of 5." aiamm530R, Mar 16, 1980; aiamm530R (Box 57, Box 19)
  - Georgetown St. Patrick's Day (Tape 2). aiamm1253C, Mar 17, 1980; aiamm1253C (Box 67, Box 44)
  - "Irish Concert - Tape 1: Celtic Thunder, Tim Britton, Fr. Charlie Coen." aiamm535R, Apr 19, 1980; aiamm535R (Box 58, Box 19)
  - "Irish Concert - Tape 2: One Song of Joe Heaney, Ceili at the End of the Evening." aiamm534R, Apr 19, 1980; aiamm534R (Box 58, Box 19)
  - "Irish Concert – Tape 3." Concert performance in a large hall by Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo, mandolin and vocals), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle). (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm532R, Apr 19, 1980; aiamm532R (Box 55, Box 16)
  - "Irish Concert - Tape 4: Joe Heaney, Moloney and O'Donnell, Celtic Thunder." aiamm533R, Apr 19, 1980; aiamm533R (Box 19, Box 58)
  - "Irish Concert - Tape 5." Music for a ceili performed by Mick Moloney (banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Linda Hickman (flute), unidentified accordion, piano, whistle, pipes. (Length: 00:20:00). aiamm531R, Apr 19, 1980; aiamm531R (Box 55, Box 16)
  - Session in Cleveland, OH. Musicians: Tom Byrne (flute), Tom McCaffrey (fiddle), Jimmy Noonan (flute, whistle). (One CD – Length: 00:15:27) aiamm3R, Apr 27, 1980; aiamm3R (Box 6, Folder 14, Box 28, Box 8)
  - "Chicago Session: Tom Ward's etc. and Interview with Jimmy and Eleanor Neary." aiamm536R, May 2, 1980; aiamm536R (Box 58, Box 19)
  - Nashville Concert. Concert performance by Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo) and Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) in Nashville, TN. (Length: 01:30:00). aiamm921C, May 10, 1980; aiamm921C (Box 39, Box 25)
  - O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle) and Moloney, Mick (banjo, guitar, mandolin, vocals). Concert performance in Nashville, TN. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:26:02) aiamm219C, May 10, 1980; aiamm219C (Box 6, Folder 15, Box 34, Box 11)
  - "Philadelphia: Tony O'Sullivan, Kevin Barnard, Timmy Britton, Mark Simos." aiamm922C, Jul 14, 1980; aiamm922C (Box 55, Box 27)
  - Port Townsend Session. Session in Washington state with Moloney and Billy McComiskey (accordion). (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm923C, Aug 30, 1980; aiamm923C (Box 55, Box 25)
  - "Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - Fiddle Workshop." Musicians include Liz Carroll and Johnny McGreevy. aiamm924C, Sep, 1980; aiamm924C (Box 27, Box 55)
  - McMahon, Tony (accordion), Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals) Concert performance on McMahon's first trip to America at the Eagle Tavern, New York, NY. (Part one of two) (Length:01:00:00). aiamm925C, Oct 29, 1980; aiamm925C (Box 26, Box 39)
  - McMahon, Tony (accordion), Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals) Concert performance on McMahon's first trip to America at the Eagle Tavern, New York, NY. (Part two of two) (Length:00:15:00) aiamm926C, Oct 29, 1980; aiamm926C (Box 55, Box 26)
  - Irish Tradition (group) Pub concert performance by Billy McComiskey (accordion), Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Andy O'Brien (guitar, vocals) at Tom O'Reilly's Pub. (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm927C, Oct, 1980; aiamm927C (Box 26, Box 58)
  - "Ballisodare Folk Festival II." Concert performances by Stockton's Wing, Paul Brady, Ossian and Jimmy Crowley. (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm928C, circa 1980; aiamm928C (Box 58, Box 26)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. "Afternoon Concert." Performances by Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Eleanor Neary (piano), Paddy Reynolds (fiddle), Irish Tradition. (Length: 01:00:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center. aiamm916C, 1980; aiamm916C (Box 25, Box 39)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Evening Concert #1." Performances by Eleanor Neary (piano) and Paddy Reynolds (fiddle), Egan Family, Joe Heaney (vocals). (Length: 01:30:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center. aiamm917C, 1980; aiamm917C (Box 55, Box 25)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Evening Concert #2." Performances by John Vesey (fiddle) and Eddie Cahill (flute), Liz Carroll (fiddle) and Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo), Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo) and Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Tim Britton and Bill Ochs (uilleann pipes). (Length: 01:00:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center. aiamm918C, 1980; aiamm918C (Box 25, Box 39)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Evening Concert #3." Performances by Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Bill Ochs (uilleann pipes) and Mark Simos (guitar), Irish Tradition, Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo, guitar) and Billy McComiskey (accordion), Tom Byrne (flute), Tom McCaffrey (flute) and Martin Mulhaire (accordion) and final session.(Length: 01:30:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center. aiamm919C, 1980; aiamm919C (Box 55, Box 25)
  - "Port Townsend: Cape Breton Tunes, Ferrell & Levy." aiamm920C, 1980; aiamm920C (Box 55, Box 27)
  - Long Note. "2nd Program." Radio show hosted by Moloney profiling Ed Reavy. (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm1217C, Jan 19, 1981; aiamm1217C (Box 26, Box 41)
  - Radio Shows. Side A: Aidan O'Hara and Moloney discuss the six Long Note programs Moloney is about to host. (1/7/81) Side B: Moloney's third Long Note program profiling the Irish Tradition. (1/26/81) (Length: 01:30:00). aiamm1218C, Jan 7 and 26, 1981; aiamm1218C (Box 26, Box 41)
  - Long Note. "4th Program." Radio show hosted by Moloney profiling Irish music in Philadelphia. (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm1219C, Feb 2, 1981; aiamm1219C (Box 41, Box 26)
  - NAFFM Concert. Musicians: Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals, mandolin), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle, recitation). Concert performance in Nashville, TN. (Two CDs – Total length: 01:36:23) aiamm313C, Feb 6, 1981; aiamm313C (Box 34, Box 6, Folder 16, Box 12)
  - Willie Clancy Summer School Benefit Concert. Musicians: Celtic Thunder, Paddy Reynolds (fiddle), Louise Chalet (guitar), Liam Og O'Flynn (uilleann pipes), Unidentified (accordion, fiddle, piano), Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo), Irish Tradition: Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Andy O'Brien (guitar, vocals), Daithi Sproule (guitar, vocals). Concert performance at George Washington University, Washington, D.C. to benefit the Willie Clancy Summer School. (Four CDs – Total length: 02:31:32) aiamm196C, Apr 10, 1981; aiamm196C (Box 11, Box 34, Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Egan Family; Philadelphia. aiamm1255C, Jun 3, 1981; aiamm1255C (Box 67, Box 44)
  - Session at the Gandy Dancer, Baltimore, MD. Musicians include: Dessie Wilkinson (flute), Mick Moloney (mandolin, banjo), Unidentified (whistle, fiddle, dulcimer, guitar, accordion) (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1212C, Jul 4, 1981; aiamm1212C (Box 64, Box 26)
  - "Boston Session. Seamus Connolly et al." aiamm1204C, Jul, 1981; aiamm1204C (Box 27, Box 64)
  - Milwaukee Session. Musicians include Liz Carroll (fiddle), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mick Moloney (banjo), Kevin Burke (fiddle). aiamm939C, Aug, 1981; aiamm939C (Box 55, Box 27)
  - Session in Milwaukee, WI. Musicians include: Sean McGlynn, Jackie Daly (accordions), Kevin Burke, Liz Carroll (fiddles), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Mick Moloney (banjo), Micheal O'Domhnaill (guitar). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:04:22) aiamm19R, Aug 1981; aiamm19R (Box 28, Box 8, Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Long Note. Irish radio program hosted by Moloney about the Irish recording industry in the US in the 1970s with profiles of Green Linnet and Shanachie including an interview with Shanachie co-founder Dan Collins. (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm940C, Sep 2, 1981; aiamm940C (Box 26, Box 40)
  - Long Note. Two episodes of Irish radio program hosted by Moloney. Side A: Palatines and Flanagan Brothers with Mike Flanagan interviews. Side B: Moloney retrospective with review of album, Strings Attached. (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm938C, Feb 16, 1981 and Sep 3, 1981; aiamm938C (Box 26, Box 40)
  - "Gaelic Festival Cassette 1." Concert performance by Blended Scotch, Norman and Nancy Blake, Mick Moloney (banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) in Knoxville, TN. (Length: 02:00:00). aiamm1215C, Oct 17, 1981; aiamm1215C (Box 26, Box 41)
  - "Gaelic Festival Cassette 2." Concert performance by Mick Moloney (banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) with Blended Scotch. (Length: 00:40:00). aiamm1216C, Oct 17, 1981; aiamm1216C (Box 26, Box 41)
  - DeDanann at the Cherry Tree. Concert performance at the Cherry Tree Folk Co-op, Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Frankie Gavin (fiddle, flute), Jackie Daly (accordion), Johnny "Ringo" McDonagh (bodhran, bones), Alec Finn (bouzouki), Maura O'Connell (vocals). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:25:04) aiamm161C, Oct 1981; aiamm161C (Box 34, Box 10, Box 6, Folder 19)
  - "Blended Scotch - Knoxville." aiamm936C, 1981; aiamm936C (Box 27, Box 57)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Spring Concert - "Tape 1." Concert performances in Philadelphia, PA from Maureen Fitzpatrick (fiddle), Brian Conway (fiddle), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Andy McGann (fiddle), Joe Burke (accordion), Lori Cole (piano). Tape plays back too fast. (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm929C, 1981; aiamm929C (Box 58, Box 26)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Spring Concert - "Tape 2." Concert performances in Philadelphia, PA from Maureen Fitzpatrick (fiddle), Brian Conway (fiddle), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Andy McGann (fiddle), Joe Burke (accordion), Lori Cole (piano). Tape plays back too fast. (Length: 01:20:00) aiamm930C, 1981; aiamm930C (Box 57, Box 26)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - Duets/Afternoon Concert - "Tape 3." Side A: Mike Rafferty and Jack Coen (flutes), John Kelly and Danny Flynn (Philadelphia Ceili Group musicians) play for dance demonstration; Side B: Concert performances by Joe and John Vesey (fiddles), Eileen Ivers (fiddle) and Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar). (Length: 01:00:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center. aiamm931C, 1981; aiamm931C (Box 26, Box 39)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Afternoon Concert - Tape 4." Performances by Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo, guitar) and Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Guilday and Roslyn Briley (harps), Martin and Brendan Mulvihill (fiddles) with Andy O'Brien (vocals, guitar). (Length: 00:50:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center. aiamm932C, 1981; aiamm932C (Box 26, Box 39)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Afternoon Concert - Tape 5." Performances by Touchstone, Dolores Keane (vocals), John Faulkner (guitar, vocals) and Eamon Curran (flute). (Length: 00:45:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center. aiamm933C, 1981; aiamm933C (Box 57, Box 26)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Evening Concert." Performances by teenaged Eileen Ivers (fiddle) and Joanie Madden (flute), Dolores Keane (vocals), John Faulkner (vocals, guitar) and Eamon Curran (flute). (Length: 01:00:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center. aiamm934C, 1981; aiamm934C (Box 57, Box 26)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Evening Concert." Performances by the Egan family including 12-year old Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Mark Simos (guitar), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen and Mike Rafferty (flutes), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo) and Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) (Length: 01:00:00) Original tapes at. American Folklife Center. aiamm935C, 1981; aiamm935C (Box 26, Box 40)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. "Tape 2 - Duets." Labeled "Mick this tape is shit." aiamm937C, 1981; aiamm937C (Box 55, Box 27)
  - Side A: Moloney, Mick and Joe A. McVernon at Fleidh; Side B: Conversations at Home. aiamm1278C, Jul 1981-Jan 1982; aiamm1278C (Box 68, Box 44)
  - Concert in Geneva, NY. Musicians: Sean McGlynn (accordion, whistle), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, vocals), Steve Gallagher, Laura Kelly (dancers). (Two CDs – Total length: 01:35:00) aiamm310C, 1982; aiamm310C (Box 34, Box 12, Box 6, Folder 20)